Oh, no, no, no, no!
Can I just donate? Can I just donate?
Close the door.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Make it scary, scary, scary.
I am!
A-ha-ha-ha!
Aah!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
It's okay, there was nothing funny
I'm laughing so hard I'm crying
Osaka Presents Game Live
Wow!
Ha-ha-ha!
Yes, I usually like to watch live video games.
So today I'd like to show you a game I'd like our members to play.
So today, I'd like to ask you to play a game that I'd like our members to play.
So, this is the person I'd like to have play this time.
Ta-da!
- Thank you very much.
Yabba mouth. Thank you.
- Did you put this on? Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
- So this time, yes, yes, yes.
- Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
- I'd like you to play.
- By the way, yes...
- By the way...
What about horror as a game genre?
I'm not good at games.
I'm really bad at horror games.
Really?
I'm not good at the "wow" type games, and I haven't played many of them.
Well, that's why I asked you to try your hand at a horror game.
But after this game we are going to play today,
There is also a live-and-play game that we are going to play today.
Are you a big fan?
Yes, there is a girl who is a big fan.
I'm going to be watching with him this time.
Come here.
Hello.
I'm Heiho.
Hiraho.
Are you a big fan?
Yes, I am.
I heard you were playing this game today.
I came here.
Oh!
Well, I'm looking forward to it.
Excuse me for interrupting.
So, the game we're going to play is called
Five Nights at Freddy's!
Wow!
This game is called
You're a night guard at a pizza parlor.
Yes, sir.
The dolls go bump in the night.
And you have to stop them from breaking in.
Prevent?
Yeah, that's right.
Yes, sir.
And the hours are midnight to 6:00 a.m.?
So, if we don't get attacked, we've succeeded.
That's easy.
What?
Sorry, it's a horror game.
There might not even be a con.
I'm really sorry about that.
It's really painful.
By the way, I heard there's a movie about this.
What's the movie about?
It was just yesterday.
Yesterday?
I saw a movie. It's a movie.
It's on right now.
Yes, it's funny.
Was it scary?
What kind of movie?
It was scary.
The screamer.
That one?
Yeah, that's him.
Screaming?
Are you okay?
New game then.
Yes, sir.
Let's get started.
It's not that hard.
Let's play Family Pizza Dial Cooking.
Day 1
First night.
You're watching this, right?
I'll be there watching the surveillance cameras.
Maybe not yet.
I think there's something called a door and a light.
The door can be bypassed by closing it when they come in.
The lights let you see if they're nearby.
But if you use it too much.
But if you use it too much, the battery in the lower left corner will run out.
So we'll have to keep an eye on it.
It's not moving.
It's much, much closer.
You have to watch it all day.
That's good.
The three that we just saw...
They're going to attack us.
They're right here.
That's them.
Maybe we should do it this way.
They're not moving at all.
Look at the battery.
When the battery runs out...
If the battery runs out, it's all dark.
You have to be a little careful.
If it doesn't work, it won't work.
It's easy to operate.
It's not that hard to operate.
You can do it.
It's not moving.
It's not moving, so it's scary.
Why isn't it moving?
We're being stymied.
Oh, what?
The cupcake from the movie.
Which one?
The yellow one, the pink one.
What? What's that?
That one?
That's it.
Oh, it came out?
It came out.
I didn't know you were from home.
Is this kind of a scene from a movie?
Yes, they do.
Yes, it is.
It's true.
She's not moving.
It's not moving.
It's not moving at all.
- It's moving! It's moving too fast! Oh, man! It's going too fast!
Where are we on the minutes?
- There's a clock above me. So, 2:00 A.M., or is it 20 now?
That means 6:00 is the end of the first night.
That's a long time.
- It's only the first night. It's a long time.
It's only the first night.
So unless we move on from this, we're not coming here, right?
We haven't moved on.
They won't come.
Does this music mean anything to you?
Maybe it's just a hint.
They're not coming.
What's the matter? Are you tired?
It's 3:00.
I think he means "Celebrate.
Is that right?
- It's working! What?
- What?
- It's moving!
It's moving.
- But it's still far away. Still far away. Still far away. Interesting!
- Hey, one more time, okay? One time? One time? One time?
It's moving.
It's finally starting to move at 3:00 a.m.
Three more to go, three more to go, three more hours.
- I can see... you're looking at me.
- Yes, very funny. What is her name?
Which one?
- This one? Bonnie? The bunny? Bonnie? Bonnie?
Bonnie's moving.
Bonnie, I'm only at 56%!
Can you stop poking around?
The lights consume more energy.
Yeah, and the doors consume more energy when they're closed all the time.
That's right.
Bonnie!
I'm watching.
It's 4:00, 4:00, two hours to go, but we're halfway there.
I don't think it's gonna make a difference. It's 4:00.
Bonnie! Bonnie! Bonnie! Bonnie!
Bonnie? Bonnie! Bonnie!
I see her!
Isn't that Hoxie? Hoxie! Hoxie! Bonnie? Hoxie bonnie?
Is that a hokey? Bonnie? Bonnie! Bonnie! Bonnie! Bonnie! Bonnie! Bonnie! Bonnie! Bonnie! Bonnie! Bonnie!
Hey, Bonnie again! Bonnie! Bonnie! Bonnie! Bonnie! Bonnie! Bonnie! Bonnie! Are we close? Close? Bonnie?
Get it over with! We'll be back later, but it looks like there's no change.
Bonnie, are we getting closer? Is that what I think it is?
Narrator, Heber!
Where are the five? Are they back?
They're back.
Why are they back?
I'm just trying to scare them.
It's getting closer, yo.
Buber, it's okay, this won't go away.
I can't bear the loss of even one day.
bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye!
вами
Boo boo, what basement do you want the lead already?
Blesh is the one the chick used to get off the ground!
A bear named Freddy, a lady named Freddy, is a good girl
Don't worry, he'll come right up to you.
You'd be surprised what you can get away with.
Where'd he go?
Oooooh...
- Game one is over! Thank you!
- Is it really big?
- Yay!
- It's the second day!
- It's the second day! It's the second day!
- You can't keep watch!
- I can't keep watch! Oh, I'm on the phone already!
- I'm still on the phone at first.
- FOXY comes at a moment's notice, doesn't it?
- I think it's important that we get a good look at the place.
- COCON
Great!
Soul Temporary Organization
I didn't say that, Manami.
I'm sure there are 3 of us.
EulerBows: Are you sure you're there correctly?
Fussa is good if you check that carefully
Oh no, it's still like this 88 per day, every day is Billy Three in the family in the recirly lease!
I think it's earlier than that.
So, jetzt.
Fone foods, sangat expectations...
Chikachan, right from the right!
This is why Chika-chan lost her fluffy charge and also went to the car Buddha is a bit of a sentence
rainbow
I want to say stuff in the body to pay yeah
I can't say go here fortress
I wonder where they went when they weren't in the middle of the concentration No, apparently they're going to close
No, apparently it's closed.
I can't tell you where it's going...
I'll be right next to you.
Bonnie, watch the charge and move!
I'll take care of it.
Bonnie, the other kids...
I can't see them!
Wait a minute!
- Aah! Wait, wait, wait, wait! I'm scared, I'm scared!
- Hold on! Hold on! Wait one more time!
- Where's Monny?
- Where's Monny? Monny! Monny! Come out!
- Monny, come out!
- Monny, come out! Monny, come out! I can't see a thing.
- Monny? Monny!
- Monny, where's...
- Get away from me!
Polly, where are you?
That's how we get around them.
That's great! That means you're evasive.
There she is! You're here! You're here!
I'm too much!
Polly, Polly, Polly, Polly, Polly, Polly, Polly, Polly, Polly, Polly, Polly.
You scared me.
Yay!
Who else? Oh! There's Pokuchy!
Pokuchy and Chika-chan!
I'm scared, I'm scared...
Sad, sad, sad.
Wait a minute, where's Bonnie?
Oh, my God!
I'm sorry, that's great.
Ituation.
Too many seats?
Bonnie got out once.
You can tell by this window if she's still there or not.
Right here, right here.
You see?
Where's Bonnie?
Oh, my God!
She's still here!
She's here now!
This is when she's still here!
But we're only at 16%!
Only 15% to go!
It's only 4:00! Now!
Come on, come on, come on!
Now?
I can't hear you at all, so I'll be fine for now.
I can't hear you at all, so I'll leave it at that. You're looking at me all smug again.
Blue, you don't have a thing about today... just a little pony...
I knew it!
Me... me...
Me!
There!
Hurry up, hurry up, hurry up!
Oh, my God.
I've never seen a battery before.
What do you mean?
The battery's dead.
The battery's dead. The battery's dead.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
I can't give you the time or anything.
The battery's dead.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no!
Oh, no.
Just go!
God!
- Oh, my God! That's great! That's great! What? Bear, who are you? Who is it?
- Freddie. I've never seen that before.
- What? Really? I knew it.
By the way, when the battery dies, it's best not to move it.
- Oh, really? Is that so? Because I'm scared.
- Yeah, I'm afraid.
Oh, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
Oh! You're early!
- Oh, he's gone.
- And they're moving fast, aren't they? Already.
- What are you doing? Chica?
What a cute name.
The battery died a little while ago.
- I was just thinking...
- I've been thinking.
Eleven o'clock. Eleven o'clock, isn't it?
- Is this 13:00 or 1:00? That's...
- It's going to be one.
- I won't look until it's one.
- Oh, what?
Oh, no?
Let's see.
What, you want to see it?
You should see it.
Let's see, chica.
Chica, she's gone.
Chica, where are you going?
I hear Chica to the right.
Oh, it's so close.
So close!
He's got his face on it.
It's so close.
What's that expression?
That's amazing.
What kind of face is that?
It's a strange face.
Chica!
Chica, where are you?
Chica.
Chica, do you like to exercise?
What makes you say that?
Do you like sports? Because you're fast, aren't you?
Chica.
Chica, please, I'm sorry, I'll give you my knee.
We're down to 1G.
I don't know where Chica is.
Oh, no, Chica!
You're getting closer.
Chika-chan's getting closer.
We're gonna get hit.
They're gonna get us. They're gonna get us.
We're not gonna get hit.
Closer, closer, closer.
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
They're coming for the door.
Not yet.
It's okay, it's okay.
Oh, my God, he's staring at me. Deer! The battery's dying!
Still no battery!
Nice evasive maneuver, Shika-chan!
Deer! You've been here the whole time!
No Bonnie, no Bonnie, no Foxy, no Foxy...
There's a little noise.
Oh, no!
Deer!
Bonnie?
Oh, there it is. Bonnie's here.
She's here, she's here, she's here, she's here, she's here.
Chica, I know you're running low on power.
Oh, she's not here.
Come on, it's 3:00.
Oh, Bonnie's close.
Oh, shit.
Bonnie, Bonnie, Bonnie.
I told you not to shoot the scissors.
Oh, my God. You just heard that, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
Nice, nice.
Oh, it's over.
Pico's body.
Look at your smug face.
Which one comes first?
- Which one's coming first? -Which one's coming first?
Chica, I can hear you.
Your heart is beating fast.
You're here, aren't you, little chicka?
- The sound... the sound is great! Oh... oh... oh... oh...
- No, no, no, no! No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no! Oh...
oh... oh... oh... oh... oh... oh... oh... oh... oh... oh... oh... oh... oh... oh! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh!
I'm afraid
Yes, help me I'm afraid of regret but I
Help me - I'm getting it
All right, ah, tickle, tickle, tickle
mmm
So much more, underground, underground, underground
Yay!
Tommy Bly Sherry
It's been an awesome fourth day... and we're really going strong.
Okay, caller, everyone's here.
I hope you've been sitting nice.
I just saw that girl in the basement move so much...
I can't see the quiet 1C.
That's not fair.
I heard footsteps.
Is this Foxy?
They're all gone!
I'm looking at them right now.
You were staring at them.
Really?
I've already seen it.
Sorry, Kira's not here either.
I've been watching so much.
Wait, wait, wait.
Music!
This way, come on.
Wow, that's scary.
I hear voices.
Screeching.
Wait a minute!
Stop! Stop!
Are you okay?
Oh, there she is.
Bonnie. Bonnie.
One o'clock.
75% at 1:00.
Isn't that fast?
That's not good.
Is it early?
I don't think the right one's coming. Bonnie, are you sure it's not coming?
I'm getting the feeling that... Oh, my God! Bonnie's dropping!
Chica, she's looking at me! She's staring at me!
Foxy's moving. Bonnie's a little fast.
Foxy is so fast.
She's going fast.
Foxy.
Foxy's still a little hard to read. Foxy hasn't been here once.
Bonnie's here, too. Foxy's dead? I didn't see her, did you?
Why the smile storm? Game over.
Foxy.
If the curtains were gaping open, it means Foxy came out.
You have to see it right then and there.
I've got a plan.
I've got a plan... now that we can see the camera.
We'll just keep an eye on Foxy and the curtains.
And if she does show up, maybe we can use lights or sound to see her.
Maybe last year?
I'm sure of it. Thank you very much.
Thank you.
If Foxy's here now...
I'll see you later.
I can't hear you.
Not yet. It sounds fine.
Can I take a look at that? Right here.
Right there.
Okay, chica.
Now, we know that Bonnie comes from the left, and Chica comes from the right.
Chica, you know she's coming from this way, too, but you only see her this way in the window.
Yes.
Then they won't come this way. Hey, it's about time. Foxy's on the move.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait! Foxy, Oaksy!
Let's hear the sound. Foxy's fast, isn't she?
But if the curtains are gone, it's probably best to close the door and let the guides do their job.
I'll be watching every now and then.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten. Foxy.
Ten, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten. Foxy.
Once every 10 seconds, Foxy.
Nine, eight, nine, ten. Foxy.
oh wow!
Su não
n e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e
e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e e
na na na na na na
4 fold pen dried
Helicar
me
e voodoo
Love you!
and Ba!]
- You're so close! Close!
- You want to give it a try?
- I'm scared!
- Yeah!
Come on, go for it.
I got it, I got it.
1CFoxy.
Scary. Scary.
One C, one C.
Oh, it's a little open.
Yes, sir.
1CFoxy.
OneCFoxy.
1CFoxy
Good. Saving power. Saving power is important.
Yes, I'm fine.
You're early.
This one and this one.
Warming up for practice.
Below are the lights.
Above is the door.
Lights.
They sang "Lights.
Do you usually play computer games like this?
Well, I've always wanted to play them.
But I don't have one yet.
I see.
I'm looking at her book, too.
It's okay, it's okay.
What? You're panicking, mmm-hmm, about the voice.
Oh, no, no, no, no! Oh, no, no, no, no!
He's not here. He's not here.
He's gone. Is he here?
I enter the house when the recessed door is open.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
Don't laugh at me!
Ha-ha-ha.
I shouldn't even use the light in there, right?
It's been 39 minutes, Sanjeev.
Three hours to go. But I'm scared.
I don't know what's going on, but I'm scared.
If she's here, maybe she'll go this way.
No, I don't think so.
She'll come when she comes.
I hope she's here.
If I see her one more time...
You're here.
Underground.
Oh, no! Oh no, no, no!
2A.
2A2A.
Dark.
But you know, I just closed both ends.
The power supply.
The battery.
They're gone, they're gone, they're gone.
It's coming from both ends, isn't it?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Red.
I've only lost 45 games due to the content of the game.
I've got mi, dly, feday, and here's the first of the colors, and I've got a little bit of a crush on you.
Aso plus a and me
Ootatsu only
Aaaaaaah!
Awww!
If there was, I would not have done it already.
hahaha
Ha-ha-ha-ha
I'm glad I didn't get hit too hard. Last chance is a good thing.
I'll say it one last time and really go for it!
Everyone's here.
I hope they'll be nice to each other.
Freddy's not coming, is he? Freddy's... surprisingly perky.
He's very active.
Foxy foxy.
Hey, Foxy Foxy.
Shee-chi, ah, you.
Foxy foxy.
Awww.
Oh, shorts work.
Oh my God, that sounded really loud.
Sound.
Oh, I see it. It's this way.
Oh, there's some snow here, too.
Oh, it's close, it's close, it's close, it's close, it's close.
ouais delicious also close close close close close close close
You're trying to move, even I'm going to go to
står, it's getting closer to where it tastes good, it's getting closer to where it plays, and I don't do AmazonPro.
I'm not going to do AmazonPro
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, 1234.
I'm okay here.
I'm just a little bit closer to where I've been I'm sorry
I don't know whose it is...
Bonnie, it's ok, Freddy's ok too, there's no one in the basement.
Freddy's not really Freddy.
Drop right, drop right!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Scary, right.
Almost there.
Oh, wow.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Here it comes.
Fifth and final. Are you ready to go?
I'm going to the end of the line. I'm going to the end of the line.
You can cry, you can laugh, you can smile.
Yes, sexy.
Oh, my God, that's amazing!
Oh, my God.
I was so focused, I didn't say anything.
We're over the hump.
But you didn't even move.
That's right.
That was fast.
You're early.
Who's there?
Who? Who?
Player?
I don't know what you're talking about.
What's that? What's that sound?
Who's that? Who's there? Where are you?
He's saying something.
What's that noise? It's so loud.
It's really loud in my ears.
Is he just trying to scare me?
He's not here.
It's touching me.
Is it Deer or Bonnie?
I knew it! Chica's there!
Yeah, yeah...
But she's early...
The presents are on their way.
Maybe it's not...
That's right. Is that possible?
I know, I know. It's not a good idea to be so impatient.
It's not a good idea, is it?
I just know it's moving. Freddy's moving.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
BOLLY.
I've seen this a million times and it still scares the shit out of me.
I'm sorry, I lied.
Wow, no!
It's getting really hard. All at once.
I had no idea where Bolly was going.
I didn't know.
I didn't even look at the camera.
What did you see? Holaib.
Surprisingly well.
It's more frustrating than scary when you get focused.
How was it yesterday? Holaib
I had a great time.
Are you glad you came? I said, "Yes, I'm glad I came.
Let's do it again.
Let's do it again!
So, everyone, please subscribe to our channel
And please give us a "Good" button.
Thank you very much.
Bye, bye, bye.